Wallen, Saul Papers 5012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Saul Wallen Papers
1935-1973
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wallen, Saul
5012
118.5 cubic feet
118.5 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
3113019
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, October 02, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 28, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5106: Connecticut Railway and Lighting Company Arbitration Files 5112: International Railway Company and the Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Local 1342 and 1386 Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Cases; Wallen, Saul, 1910-1969; Air Carrier Mechanics Association; Airline Stewards and Stewardesses Association; Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corporation; Aluminum Company of America; Aluminum Trades Council; Aluminum Workers International Union; Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America; Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America; Amalgamated Transit Union; American Airlines; American Brass Company; American Communications Association; American Federation of Technical Engineers; American Hide and Leather Company; Association of Engineers, Architects and Draftsmen; Association of Scientists and Professional Engineering Personnel; B.F. Goodrich Company; Beggs & Cobb, Inc.; Bethlehem Steel Corporation; Borden Company; Boston Edison Company; Borg-Warner Corporation. Warner Gear Division.; Boston Gear Works; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes; Browne and Sharpe Manufacturing Company; C.B. Hydron; Celanese Chemical Company; Chemtron Corporation; Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company; Clifford Manufacturing, Inc.; Creese and Cook Company; Crestband Leather Company; Curtiss-Wright Corporation; Draper Corporation; Eastern Air Lines; Fafnir Bearing Program; Fermon Leather Company; General Tire & Rubber Co.; Ford Motor Company; Gas and By-Products Coke Workers; General Cable Corporation; General Motors Corporation; Greyhound Corporation; Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America; International Air Line Pilots Association; International Association of Machinists; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers.; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; International Chemical Workers Union; International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada; International Shoe Company; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers.; International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; International Union, United Automobile Workers of America (A.F. of L.); J.S. Barnet and Sons; Jones and Lamson Machine Company; Kaiser Steel Corporation; Kirstein Leather Company; Leather Workers International Union of America; Massachusetts Leather Manufacturers Association; Monsanto Chemical Works; National Coordinating Board; National Standard Company; New York City Transit Authority; Northwest Airlines Corporation; Office and Clerical Employees. American Bridge Division.; Office Employees International Union; Order of Railroad Telegraphers (U.S.); Oxford Paper Company; Pan American World Airways, Inc.; Pratt & Whitney Company; Radio Corporation of America; Raytheon Company; Raytheon Guards Association; Republic Steel Corporation; Scott and Williams, Inc.; Scovill Manufacturing Company; Southern Airways, Inc.; Southern Pacific Company; Sylvania Electric Products, Inc.; Textile Workers Union of America; Trailways of New England, Inc.; Trans World Airlines; Transport Workers Union of America; Union Street Railway Company; Union Twist Drill Company; United Air Lines, Inc.; United Construction Workers; United Papermakers and Paperworkers; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America; United Shoe Workers of America; United States. National War Labor Board (1942-1945); United States Corporation Company; United Steelworkers of America; Utility Workers Union of America; Verza Tanning Company; Walworth Company; Waterbury Brass Workers Union; Western Airlines; Western Union Telegraph Company; Winslow Brothers and Smith
3113019
- Steven Abrants, North Smithfield R.I. 4/l4/47 - Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp., Brackenridge Works, 12/2/64 (Box 1-3)
  - Steve Abrants and Textile Workers Union of America 4/14/47, 1947 (Box 1-3, Folder 1)
  - Alco Products, Inc. and United Steelworkers, 1968 (Box 1-3, Folder 2)
  - Alco Products, Inc., Latrobe, Pa. United Steelworkers Dist. 19, 1966 (Box 1-3, Folder 3)
  - Alden Storage Co., Boston and United Textile Workers, 1960 (Box 1-3, Folder 4)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Brackenridge and United Steelworkers Local 1196, 1954 (Box 1-3, Folder 5)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, W. Leechburg and United Steelworkers, Local 1138, 1956 (Box 1-3, Folder 6)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Brackenridge and United Steelworkers, Local 1196, 1960 (Box 1-3, Folder 7)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Pittsburgh and United Steelworkers, 1957 (Box 1-3, Folder 8)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Corp., Wallingford and United Steelworkers, 1962 (Box 1-3, Folder 9)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Corp., Wallingford and United Steelworkers, 1962 (Box 1-3, Folder 10)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Corp., Wallingford and United Steelworkers, 1962 (Box 1-3, Folder 11)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Brackenridge and United Steelworkers, 1963 (Box 1-3, Folder 12)
  - Allegheny Ludlum Steel, Watervliet and United Steelworkers, Local 2478, 1963 (Box 1-3, Folder 13)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Watervliet and United Steelworkers, Local 2478, 1963 (Box 1-3, Folder 14)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Watervliet and United Steelworkers, Local 2478, 1963 (Box 1-3, Folder 15)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Watervliet and United Steelworkers, 1963 (Box 1-3, Folder 16)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Watervliet and United Steelworkers, Local 2478, 1963 (Box 1-3, Folder 17)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Watervliet and United Steelworkers, Local 2478, 1963 (Box 1-3, Folder 18)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Dunkirk and United Steelworkers, Local 2963, 1963 (Box 1-3, Folder 19)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Dunkirk and United Steelworkers, Local 2693, 1964 (Box 1-3, Folder 20)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Dunkirk and United Steelworkers, Local 2693, 1964 (Box 1-3, Folder 21)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Watervliet and United Steelworkers, Local 2478, 1963-1964 (Box 1-3, Folder 22)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Brackenridge and United Steelworkers Local 1196, 1964 (Box 1-3, Folder 23)
  - Alleghany Ludlum corp., Brackenridge and United Steelworkers, Local 1196, 1964 (Box 1-3, Folder 24)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp., Brackenridge, Penn., 12/3/64 - Aluminum Co. of America, Davenport Works, 12/9/60 (Box 4-6)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Brackenridge and United Steelworkers, Local 1196, 1964 (Box 4-6, Folder 1)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Wallingford and United Steelworkers Local 2242, 1964 (Box 4-6, Folder 2)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Wallingford and United Steelworkers, Local 2242, 1956-1964 (Box 4-6, Folder 3)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Wallingford and United Steelworkers, Local 2242, 1965 (Box 4-6, Folder 4)
  - Allegheny Ludlum Steel, Wallingford and United Steelworkers, Local 2242, 1965 (Box 4-6, Folder 5)
  - Alleghany Ludlum Steel, Brackenridge and United Steelworkers, Local 2984, 1966 (Box 4-6, Folder 6)
  - Allen Manufacturing Company and U.A.W., Local #518, 1950 (Box 4-6, Folder 7)
  - Allen Manufacturing Company and U.A.W., Local 518, 1956 (Box 4-6, Folder 8)
  - F.M. Allen Company and International Fur and Leather, Local 20, 1954 (Box 4-6, Folder 9)
  - Allied Concrete Company and Teamsters, Local 379, 1968 (Box 4-6, Folder 10)
  - Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company and I.U.E., Local 279, 1958-1962 (Box 4-6, Folder 11)
  - Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company and I.U.E., Local 279, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 12)
  - Aluminum Company of America - Massena and Offices Employees International, 180, 1958 (Box 4-6, Folder 13)
  - Aluminum Company of America - Massena and Office Employees International, 180, 1958 (Box 4-6, Folder 14)
  - Aluminum Company of America - Massena and Office Employees International, 180, 1958 (Box 4-6, Folder 15)
  - Aluminum Company of America - Massena and Office Employees International, 180, 1955-1958 (Box 4-6, Folder 16)
  - Aluminum Company of America - Massena and Office Employees International, 180, 1958 (Box 4-6, Folder 17)
  - Aluminum Company of America - Massena and Office Employees International 180, 1959 (Box 4-6, Folder 18)
  - Aluminum Company of America - Massena and Office Employees International, 180, 1959 (Box 4-6, Folder 19)
  - Aluminum Company of America - Massena and Office Employees International, 180, 1959 (Box 4-6, Folder 20)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Davenport and Aluminum Workers, Local 105, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 21)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Davenport and Aluminum Workers, Local 105, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 22)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona and Aluminum Workers, Local 405, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 23)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Davenport and Aluminum Workers, Local 105, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 24)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Massena and Aluminum Workers, Local 420, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 25)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Massena and Aluminum Workers, Local 420, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 26)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Davenport and Aluminnum workers, Local 105, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 27)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Cressona Aluminum Workers, Local 405, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 28)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Massena and Aluminum Workers, Local 420, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 29)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Massena and Aluminum Workers, Local 420, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 30)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Davenport and Aluminum Workers, Local 105, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 31)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Davenport and Aluminum Workers, Local 105, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 32)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Davenport and Aluminum Workers International, 105, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 33)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Davenport and Aluminum Workers, Local 105, 1960 (Box 4-6, Folder 34)
- Aluminum Co. of America, Lancaster Works, 2/1/61 - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa., 6/14/62 (Box 7-9)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Lancaster and Aluminum Workers, Local 415, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 1)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Lancaster and Aluminum Workers, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 2)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Massena and Aluminum Workers Local #420, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 3)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Massena and Aluminum Workers, Local #420, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 4)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Lancaster and Aluminum Workers, Local 415, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 5)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Lafayette and Aluminum Workers, Local 115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 6)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Massena and Aluminum Workers - Local #420, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 7)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Massena and Aluminum Workers Local #420, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 8)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Lafayette and Aluminum Workers, Local #420, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 9)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Lafayette, Ind. And Aluminum Workers International Local 415, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 10)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Massena, N.Y. and Aluminum Workers International Local 420, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 11)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Lafayette and Aluminum Workers Local #115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 12)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Lafayette and Aluminum Workers, Local #115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 13)
  - Aluminum Co. of America., Lafayette, Ind. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 415, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 14)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Lafayette, Ind. And Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 15)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette Ind. And Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 16)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, Ind. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 17)
  - Aluminum Co. of America., Lafayette, Ind. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l Local 115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 18)
  - Aluminum Co. of Amer., Lafayette, Ind. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l Local 115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 19)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, Ind. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l Local 115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 20)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, Ind. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 21)
  - Aluminum Company of America, Lafayette and Aluminum Workers, Local 115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 22)
  - Aluminum Co. of Amer., Lafayette, Ind. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 115, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 23)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 405, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 24)
  - Aluminum Co. of Amer., Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers Internat'l Local 405, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 25)
  - Aluminum Co. of Amer., Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Trades Council AFL-CIO, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 26)
  - Aluminum Co. of Amer., Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Trades Council AFL-CIO, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 27)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Trades Council AFL-CIO, 1961 (Box 7-9, Folder 28)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers Internat'l Local #405, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 29)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Warrick, Ind. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 104, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 30)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, Ind. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l Local 115, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 31)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Trades Council; pf Vancouver, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 32)
  - Aluminum Co. of Amer., Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Trades Council of Vancouver, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 33)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Trades Council of Vancouver, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 34)
  - aluminum Co. of Amer, Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Trades Council of Vancouver, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 35)
  - Aluminum Co. of Amer., Lafayette, Ind. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l. Local 115, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 36)
  - Aluminum Co. of Amer., Lancaster, PA. and Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 415, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 37)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Massena, N.Y. and Aluminum Workers Internat'l Local #420, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 38)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Massena, N.Y. and Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 420, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 39)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Massena, N.Y. and Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 420, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 40)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Davenport, Iowa and Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 105, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 41)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Davenport, Iowa and Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 105, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 42)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Massena, N.Y. and Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 420, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 43)
  - Aluminum Co. of Amer., Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 405, 1962 (Box 7-9, Folder 44)
- Aluminum Co. of America, Vancouver, Wash., 10/31/62 - Aluminum Co. of America, Warrick Works, 12/10/63 (Box 10-12)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l, 1962 (Box 10-12, Folder 1)
  - Aluminum Co. of Amer., Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l Union, 1962 (Box 10-12, Folder 2)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Warrick and Aluminum Workers, Local 104, 1962 (Box 10-12, Folder 3)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l Union, 1962 (Box 10-12, Folder 4)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Workers Internat'l Union, 1962 (Box 10-12, Folder 5)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, - Warrick and Aluminum Workers, Local 104, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 6)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Warrick and Aluminum Workers, Local 104, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 7)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Warrick and Aluminum Workers, Local 104, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 8)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Workers International, Local 300, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 9)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers Internat'l, Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 10)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 11)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Wenatchee, Wash. And Aluminum Trades of Wenatchee, Wash., 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 12)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 13)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 14)
  - Aluminum Co. of America - Cressona and Aluminum Workers, Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 15)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 406, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 16)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lancaster, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 415, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 17)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 18)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lancaster, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 415, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 19)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Vancouver, Wash. And Aluminum Workers International, Local 300, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 20)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 21)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Davenport, Ia. And Aluminum Workers International, Local 105, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 22)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Davenport, Ia. And Aluminum Workers International, Local 105, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 23)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lancaster, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 415, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 24)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 25)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 26)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, I. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 27)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, I. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 28)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, I. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 29)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, I. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 30)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, I. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 31)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, I. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 32)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, I. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 33)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, I. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 34)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, I. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 35)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette, I. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 36)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 37)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lafayette and Aluminum Workers International, Local 115, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 38)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lancaster, Pa. and Aluminum Workers. International, Local 415, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 39)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Lancaster, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 415, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 40)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 41)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona, Pa. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 405, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 42)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Massena Works and Aluminum Workers International Local 420, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 43)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Massena Works and Aluminum Workers International Local 420, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 44)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Massena Works and Aluminum Workers International Local 420, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 45)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Massena, N.Y. and Aluminum Workers International, Local 420, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 46)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Warrick Works and Aluminum Workers International, Local 104, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 47)
  - Aluminum Co. of America, Warrick Works and Aluminum Workers International Local 104, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 48)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Warrick Works and Aluminum Wkrs. Int'l, Local 104, 1963 (Box 10-12, Folder 49)
- Aluminum Co. of America, Warrick Works, 12/18/63 - Aluminum Co. of America, Cressona Works, 2/9/65 (Box 13-15)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 104 - Warrick, 1963 (Box 13-15, Folder 1)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 104 - Warrick, 1963 (Box 13-15, Folder 2)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 104 - Warrick, 1963 (Box 13-15, Folder 3)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 104 - Warrick, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 4)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 104 - Warrick, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 5)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 104 - Warrick, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 6)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 104 - Warrick, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 7)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 104 - Massena, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 8)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 420 - Massena, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 9)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 405, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 10)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 405 - Cressona, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 11)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 405 - Cressona, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 12)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers Local 420 - Massena, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 13)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers International Local 105 - Davenport, Iowa, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 14)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers International Local 104 - Warrick Works, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 15)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers International Local 115 - Lafayette, Ind., 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 16)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers International Local 115 - Lafayette. Ind., 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 17)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers International Local 115 - Lafayette, Ind., 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 18)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers International Local 105 - Davenport, Iowa, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 19)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers International Local 115 - Lafayette Works, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 20)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers International Local 115 - Lafayette, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 21)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers International Local 115 - Lafayette, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 22)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers International Local 115, Lafayette, 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 23)
  - Aluminum Co. of America Aluminum Workers International Local 115, Lafayette, Ind., 1964 (Box 13-15, Folder 24)